Hey! You're that spider
guy on YouTube, right? Call
me Spider-Man! Okay Spider-Man!
Go flip! Yeah!
Not bad! Woo!
The pilot in the back
seats The generation hits The
dames in the back feet
Hey buddy! Oh!
Shouldn't steal cars is bad.
It's my car, dumbass! Hey!
Shut that off! I was
just trying to... That was
my car! You! You're working
nights! Come on, dude! That's
not your car! What am
I supposed to do with
this car? Where's the door?
It's not your car! Every
day with these damn alarms!
Shut it off! Don't make
me come down there, you
punk! Hey, Gary! How
you doing? Marjorie, how are
you? How's your mother? I'm
good. I'm good. Oh,
no. My friends are up
there. What? Uh, don't worry,
ma'am. Everything's gonna be okay.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Oh,
my God, that's tall. Oh,
my God, look at the
ceiling. Just stay calm, everyone.
Yeah, okay. Oh, yeah, I'll
bet you die here. Estimating
ten minutes before catastrophic failure.
We're freaking screwed. Okay, guys,
I know that was scary,
but our safety systems are
working. The safety systems are
completely failing. We're very safe
in here. The occupants are
in imminent mortal danger. I'm
going as fast as I
can!